[
  "You can reach Zentrix Technology through our website contact form by providing your Name, Phone Number, Email, and a message about your idea or inquiry. Our team responds within 24 hours.",
  "The Digital Marketing Intern role covers social media marketing, content creation, campaign management, email marketing, and online brand promotion across platforms like Instagram, Facebook, and LinkedIn.",
  "The Digital Marketing Intern role covers social media strategy, content creation, paid campaign management, email marketing, audience targeting, and online brand promotion across Instagram, Facebook, and LinkedIn. Duration 3 months.",
  "content marketing\nanswer   : Zentrix creates data-driven content marketing strategies including blog writing, video scripts, email campaigns, and lead generation content that drives brand visibility and customer engagement.",
  "The Zentrix contact form collects Name, Phone Number, Email, and a brief description of the project or idea. Users can submit requests through the website for services, projects, courses, or career-related inquiries."
]
